That's amazing.
凄いじゃん
No.
ダメ
Wow, that's a bit narrow.
うわ、ちょっと狭いね
It's easy to feel.
感じ やすいんだね
I'm not shy at all.
全然恥ずかしがってないよ
It might be easy to feel this way.
こう感じやすいかも
difficult.
難しい
What would happen if this happened?
これとかなってたらどうなっちゃうの?
stop?
やめる?
Should I have stopped?
やめた方が良かった?
It's really strong.
凄い強いじゃん
Maybe I haven't done it recently.
最近してなかったかも
I drank it for a moment.
一瞬間飲んだね
I think I'll go there again.
また 行っちゃいそうじゃん
You really like going there, don't you?
めっちゃ行っちゃい好きでしょ?
Are you going this far?
こんなに行っちゃうの?
Hey, I'm being sneaky when I'm talking about myself.
ちょっとさ、自分ばっか言っててずるいからさ
Not just your feet, can I touch your penis?
足だけじゃなくてさ、ちんこ触ってもらってもいい?
Is it okay if I dazzle you a little?
ちょっと眩してもらってもいいかな?
What kind of penis do you like?
どういうちんこ好きなの?
I like it hard.
硬いのが好き
Is hardness more important than length and thickness?
長さ、太さより硬さ?
Do you like hard ones?
硬いのが好きかな?
It's only about the size of your face, right?
顔の大きさのちんこぐらいしかないでしょ?
Are you going to lick it?
舐めちゃうの?
You're so cute, Feron.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いね、フェロン
Looks like it's about to come out.
出 ちゃいそうだね
That's terrible.
やばいね
I can't resist it, so let's get a pet together.
我慢できないからさ、一緒にペットいってみよう
It's already cold.
もう冷たい
This looks like Manji.
マンジみたいですね、これ
I added it, I added it,
たらしちゃった、たらしちゃった、
I did it.
たらしちゃった
stop?
やめる?
I can't stand it.
我慢できないよ
Is it okay to say it now?
もう言っていいでしょ?
I'm going to eat it.
めんごむして
Just one minute, just one minute.
1分だけ、1分だけ
No.
ダメ
I'll eat already.
もう食べる
Just 10 seconds.
10秒だけ
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
It's blowing again.
また吹いちゃってるじゃん
It's like this, it's good enough.
こんな感じで、もういいじゃん
It's going to be crazy.
めっちゃいっちゃうじゃん
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎ
Wow
うわ
Ah, that's amazing.
ぁ、 すごいね
The camera is serious today.
カメラ今日は真摯だね
Look at the camera and try your piece.
カメラに向かってピースしてみてよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's going to come out, it's going to come out.
抜けちゃう、抜けちゃう
Great, we're closing here.
すごい、ここ閉まるね
Let's go, let's go.
出ちゃう、出ちゃう
No, no
ダメ、ダ
Me.
メ
Looks like it's going to be hard.
い っちゃいそう
Something, something, doesn't feel right.
なんか、なんか、なんかダメ
Ugh, no more.
うわぁ、もうダメ
I let it out a little.
ちょっと出しちゃった
It felt so good.
気持ちよすぎて
Your friends will find out, right?
友達とかに、バレるじゃないですか
That's a good thing.
いいことじゃん
I'm not happy.
嬉しくないです
I've met you like that already.
もうあんなに会えたろ
If it felt good, we could have met, right?
気持ちよかったら会えたんじゃねえの?
It's a little bit out there.
出回るのはちょっと
That's why I came here today to check out the video.
だから今日、動画検証してこっち来たんだな
Do you want it to dawn?
夜明けしてほしいの?
I want it to disappear.
消してほしいです
Then don't listen to anything I say.
じゃあ、何でも言うこと聞くな
But if you like, I'll play.
でも、好きだったら遊ぶから
Is it okay?
いいんだろ?
yes.
はい